Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Graphic materials
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy prints negatives; AFC 2003/002: MISSING (Box-folder 65/1870-1871)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 11 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1066-PH1076 (Box-folder 65/1872-1882)
    P75.1. – P75.3. and P75.5. – P75.11.) 75.4: NOT MADE FROM ORIGINAL NEGATIVE.
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 2 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1077-PH1078 (Box-folder 65/1883-1884)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 10 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1079-PH1087 (Box-folder 65/1885-1894)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 10 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1088-PH1097 (Box-folder 65/1895-1904)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 18 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1098-PH1115 (Box-folder 65/1905-1922)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 13 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1116-PH1128 (Box-folder 66/1923-1935)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 71 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1129-PH1199 (Box-folder 66/1936-2006)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 41 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1202-PH1240 (Box-folder 66/2007-2047)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 19 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1241-PH1258 (Box-folder 66/2048-2065)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 4 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1259-PH1262 (Box-folder 66/2066-2069)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 3 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1264-PH1266 (Box-folder 66/2071-2073)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1267 (Box-folder 66/2074)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 15 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1268-PH1282 (Box-folder 66/2075-2089)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 10 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1311-PH1320 (Box-folder 66/2090-2099)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 11 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1321-PH13331 (Box-folder 66/2100-2110)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 3 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1332-PH1334 (Box-folder 66/2111-2113)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 8 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1335-PH1342 (Box-folder 66/2114-2121)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 5 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1343-PH1347 (Box-folder 66/2122-2126)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 9 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1351-PH1359 (Box-folder 66/2127-2135)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 5 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1360-PH1364 (Box-folder 66/2136-2140)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1365 (Box-folder 66/2141)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 5 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1366-PH1373 (Box-folder 66/2142-2149)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 2 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1374-PH1375 (Box-folder 66/2150-2151)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 8 copy print negatives; AFC 2003/002: PH1376-PH1383 (Box-folder 66/2152-2159)
  - Luboml 2001 Offshoot, 1 copy print negative; AFC 2003/002: PH1384 (Box-folder 66/2160)
  - Efrat, 2 negative strips; AFC 2003/002: P4 (Box-folder 67/2161)
  - Karpus, 6 negative strips; AFC 2003/002: P18 (Box-folder 67/2162)
  - Eiger, 3 negatives strips; AFC 2003/002: P28 (Box-folder 67/2163)
  - Swerdloff, 2 negatives strips; AFC 2003/002: P30 (Box-folder 67/2164)
  - Zucker, 2 negatives strips; AFC 2003/002: P31 (Box-folder 67/2165)
  - Mussenblatt, 5 negatives strips; AFC 2003/002: P33 (Box-folder 67/2166)
  - Kostin, 6 negatives strips; AFC 2003/002: P34 (Box-folder 67/2167)
  - Frankel, 1 negative strips; AFC 2003/002: P35 (Box-folder 67/2168)
  - Ora, 4 negative strips; AFC 2003/002: P36 (Box-folder 67/2169)
  - Teitlebaum, 1 negative strip; AFC 2003/002: P38 (Box-folder 67/2170)
  - Zimerberg, 4 negatives strips; AFC 2003/002: P41 (Box-folder 67/2171)
  - Golod, 4 negative strips; AFC 2003/002: P42 (Box-folder 67/2172)
  - Karous, 11 negative strips. (Box-folder 67/2173)
  - Ziegelman, 61 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2174)
  - Wasserman, 81 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2175)
    Negatives for PH1881-2068
  - Abe Getman: Boker Artifacts and Luboml 2001 Film shoot, 20 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2176)
  - Kiddush cup spice box, 7 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2177)
  - Artifacts in Exhibition, 7 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2178)
  - Goodman, Karpus, Gutman: Donors, Artifacts, 10 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2179)
  - Artifacts: Shawl, Phylacteries and bag in exhibition, 6 negative strips (Box-folder 67/2180)
  - P1.1, P1.4 (2), P1.8. Guz. Duplicate Prints, 4 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2181)
  - P2.1, P2.2, P2.3, P2.7. Shalev. Duplicate Prints, 4 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2182)
  - P5.2, P5.3, P5.4, P5.5, P5.6, P5.9, P5.12, P5.14, P5.15 (2), P5.17, P5.18, P5.20, P5.21. Ingber. Duplicate Prints, 14 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2183)
  - P6.2, P6.4, P6.5, P6.9, P6.10, P6.12, P6.13 (2). Raz. Duplicate Prints, 14 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2184)
  - P7.1 (2), P7.2, P7.9, P7.11. Blau (Weiner). Duplicate Prints, 5 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2185)
  - P8.2, P8.4 (2), P8.6, P8.10, P8.13, P8.17, P8.18, P8.19. Kandelshtein Duplicate Prints, 9 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2186)
  - P9.1, P9.7, P9.10, P9.11 (2). Shinal. Duplicate Prints, 5 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2187)
  - P10.2, P10.3, P10.4, P10.5, P10.7, P10.8 (2), P10.9, P10.10, P10.12, P10.14, P10.15 (2), P10.19, P10.20. Erlich. Duplicate Prints, 15 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2188)
  - P11.2, P11.3, P11.5, P11.6, P11.8, P11.11. Giladi. Duplicate Prints, 6 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2189)
  - P12.1, P12.3. Melamed. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2190)
  - P13.1, P13.2, P13.3. Jucht. Duplicate Prints, 3 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2191)
  - P14.1 (2), P14.2 (2), P14.4 (2), P14.5, P14.7, P14.10, P14.13, P14.14, P14.15, P14.16. Bokser. Duplicate Prints, 13 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2192)
  - P15.1, P15.2. Seidel. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2193)
  - P16.1, P16.2. Langer. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2194)
  - P17.1, P17.4, P17.5 (2), P17.6, P17.9, P17.10, P17.12 (2), P17.13, P17.16, P17.18, P17.21, P17.23, P17.24. Wolyn. Duplicate Prints, 15 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2195)
  - P18.4, P18.14, P18.39 (2), P18.41, P18.48. Karpus. Duplicate Prints, 6 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2196)
  - P23.3. Haghetaot. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 68/2197)
  - P24.6, P24.8, P24.17. Friedman. Duplicate Prints, 3 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2198)
  - P33.10. Nussenblatt. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 68/2199)
  - P39.32, P39.51, P39.54. Uberman. Duplicate Prints, 3 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2200)
  - P40.3. Montevideo. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 68/2201)
  - P41.1, P41.2, P41.3 (2). Zimerberg. Duplicate Prints, 4 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2202)
  - P42.15, P42.18, P42.30, P42.39, P42.40, P42.46, P42.48, P42.51, P42.54, P42.56, P42.59, P42.70, P42.71, P42.72, P42.73, P42.74. Golod, Duplicate Prints. (16 duplicate prints.) (Box-folder 68/2203)
  - P44.1, P44.3, P44.4, P44.9, P44.12, P44.15 (2), P44.18, P44.19, P44.24, P44.29, P44.35, P44.36, P44.39, P44.41, P44.43. Sobel, 16 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2204)
  - P45.8. Ziegelman. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 68/2205)
  - P46.8, P46.18, P46.25, P46.31, P46.32, P46.33. Chanales. Duplicate Prints, 6 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2206)
  - P47.1, P47.39, P47.41. Kessler. Duplicate Prints, 3 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2207)
  - P48.7, P48.21. Eiger. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2208)
  - P49.6, P49.19. Gershengorn. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2209)
  - P51.7. Zimmerberg. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 68/2210)
  - P52.2. Tessler. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 68/2211)
  - P54.9, P54.14, P54.19, P54.39. Getman. Duplicate Prints, 4 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2212)
  - P55.2, P55.10, P55.11, P55.13. Polska Akademia Nauk, Instytut Sztuki. Duplicate Print, 4 duplicate prints (Box-folder 68/2213)
  - P56.2, P56.3. Glickman. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2214)
  - P57.11, 57.13, 57.23, 57.36, 57.44. Bravet. Duplicate Prints, 5 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2215)
  - P58.1, P58.5, P58.6. Bokser. Duplicate Prints, 3 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2216)
  - P59.3, P59.4, P59.13, P59.15. Linder. Duplicate Prints, 4 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2217)
  - P60.3, P60.4, P60.7, P60.9 (2), P60.10. Orbuch. Duplicate Prints, 6 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2218)
  - P61.3, P61.7. Krawt. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2219)
  - P66.11, P66.16. Gutman. Duplicate Prints, 2 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2220)
  - P71.2. Rosenbluth. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2221)
  - P72.1. Gitalis. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2222)
  - P73.4, P73.9, P73.11, P73.17, P73.18, P73.20. Rosenzweig, Duplicate Prints. (6 duplicate prints) (Box-folder 69/2223)
  - P74.2. Halpern. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2224)
  - P76.1. Ginsburg. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2225)
  - P77.2. Levine. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2226)
  - P78.3, P78.5, P78.7. Meller. Duplicate Prints, 3 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2227)
  - P79.7. Schimmel. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2228)
  - P80.17. Hetman. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2229)
  - P81.9. Goodman. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2230)
  - P82.15 (2), P82.17, P82.21, P82.22, P82.28, P82.43, P82.57, P82.58, P82.63, P82.70, P82.71. Dzei. Duplicate Prints, 12 duplicate prints (Box-folder 69/2231)
  - P83.2. Ostapyuk. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2232)
  - P84.1, P84.4 (2), P84.10, P84.14. Luboml Museum. Duplicate Prints, 5 duplicate prints.) (Box-folder 69/2233)
  - P85.5. Kaminska. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2234)
  - P88.12. Borman. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2235)
  - P92.10. Prager. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2236)
  - P93.3. Samberg. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2237)
  - P96.1. Glass. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2238)
  - P99.7. Plotnik. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2239)
  - P102.8. Reimer. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2240)
  - P103.1. Newberger. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2241)
  - P105.1. Gryn. Duplicate Prints, 1 duplicate print (Box-folder 69/2242)
  - Maps, Negatives and chromes (8x10) Prints from negatives P5.1. Duplicate Prints, 6 prints (Box-folder 70/2243)
  - Maps, Negatives and chromes (8x10) Prints from negatives P5.2. Duplicate Prints, 24 prints (Box-folder 70/2244)
  - 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml: Aaron Ziegelman. Aaron Ziegelman’s photo of trip to Luboml extra prints. Duplicate Prints, 36 color prints (Box-folder 70/2245)
  - 1995 Research Expedition to Luboml: Fred Wasserman. Duplicate prints, 32 color prints (Box-folder 70/2246)
  - Luboml Exhibition Project, P.R. Photos. Duplicate prints, 22 color prints (Box-folder 70/2247)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot. Duplicate prints, 25 color prints (Box-folder 70/2248)
  - Luboml 2001 Film shoot: Wasserman. Duplicate prints, 6 color prints (Box-folder 70/2249)
  - Luboml, Pix for Fred. Duplicate for Fred. Duplicate prints, 50 color prints (Box-folder 70/2250)
- Transparencies of Artifacts
  Folders 2311-2332 contains positive transparencies of artifacts in the exhibition and scanned materials for the exhibition graphics.
  - Group of Luboml artifacts, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2251)
  - Silver cigarette case, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2252)
    Donated by Victor Gershengorn.
  - Silver cigarette case, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2253)
  - Red shawl with floral pattern, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2254)
  - Red shawl with floral pattern, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2255)
  - Sabbath candlesticks, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2256)
    Donated by Kalia Bokser
  - Sabbath candlesticks, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2257)
    Donated by Kalia Bokser.
  - Silver spoon, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2258)
    Donated by Lilian Chanales.
  - Tallis with blue thread, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2259)
    Aaron Eiger
  - Tallis with blue thread, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2260)
  - Silver kiddush cup, (2 1/2 h x 1 3/8 w) (Box-folder 71/2261)
    Donated by Karpus
  - Silver kiddush cup, (1 5/8 h x 1 1/4w ), 1 black and white transparency
    Donated by Moshe Shalev
  - Embroidered slip, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2262)
  - Curtain with lace embroidery, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2263)
  - Curtain with lace embroidery, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2264)
  - Curtain with lace embroidery, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2265)
  - Curtain with lace embroidery, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2266)
  - Silver kiddush cup, (2 1/2 h x 1 3/8 w) (Box-folder 71/2267)
  - Silver kiddush cup, (1 5/8 h x 1 1/4w ), 1 black and white transparency
    Donated by Moshe Shalev.
  - No transparency (Box-folder 71/2268)
  - Three men walking, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2269)
    Donated by Kraut.
  - Women lighting candles, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2270)
  - Couple driving, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2271)
  - Two women and a man, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2272)
  - Liquor labels form Kopelzon and Rajzmen distillery (Box-folder 71/2273)
  - Luboml Museum, 1 black and white transparency
    Donated by Mikola Dzei.
  - Wood and brass shoe remover, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2274)
  - Wood and brass shoe remover, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2275)
  - Embroidered matzoh cover, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2276)
    Donated by May Goodman.
  - Embroidered matzoh cover, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2277)
  - Embroidered matzoh cover, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2278)
  - Unmatched fork and spoon, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2279)
    Donated by Bracha Fuks.
  - Unmatched fork and spoon, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2280)
  - Unmatched fork and spoon, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2281)
  - Unmatched fork and spoon, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2282)
  - Details of fork and spoon, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2283)
  - Details of fork and spoon, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2284)
  - Silver wine cups, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2285)
    Donated by Alexander Ostapywk.
  - Silver wine cups, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2286)
  - Love poem, ca. 1941-1944, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2287)
    Written to Sonia Orbuch from a fellow partisan. Donated by Orbuch.
  - Love poem, ca. 1941-1944, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2288)
  - Love poem, ca. 1941-1944, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2289)
    Written to Sonia Orbuch from a fellow partisan. Donated by Sonia Orbuch.
  - Love poem, ca. 1941-1944, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2290)
  - Postcard (front), 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2291)
    Donated by Sonia Orbuch.
  - Postcard (back), 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2292)
  - Postcard (back), 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2293)
  - Postcard (back), 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2294)
  - Postcard (back), 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2295)
  - Bar Mitzvah celebration of Moshe and David, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2296)
    The Celebration was postponed due to the war. Donated by Sonia Orbuch
  - White cotton pajamas with blue trimming, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2301)
    Donated by Aviva Hetman.
  - Two women, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2302)
  - One woman, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2303)
  - One woman, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2304)
  - Embroidered tallis bag, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2305)
    Donated by Abraham Getman.
  - Embroidered tallis bag, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2306)
  - Phylacteries, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2307)
  - Phylacteries, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2308)
  - Family photo portrait, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2309)
    Donated by Halperin.
  - Photo portrait, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2310)
    Donated by Woyzuck.
  - Krejn's photography studio, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2311)
  - Krejn's photography studio, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2312)
  - Krejn's photography studio, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2313)
  - Ticket to the Benefit Dance, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2314)
  - Ticket to the Benefit Dance, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2315)
  - Ticket to the Benefit Dance, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2316)
  - Receipt from Grimatlicht's Mill, 1940, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2317)
  - Receipt from Grimatlicht's Mill, 1940, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2318)
  - Receipt from savings and loan of Jewish community, ca. 1920s, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2319)
  - Receipt from savings and loan of Jewish community, ca. 1920s, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2320)
  - Receipt from savings and loan of Jewish community, ca. 1920s, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2321)
  - Polish poster: call on citizens to vote, 1935, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2322)
    Donated by Luboml Museum.
  - Polish poster: call on citizens to vote, 1935, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2323)
  - Polish poster: call on citizens to vote, 1935, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2324)
  - Polish poster: announcement of military purchase of horses in market square, 1936, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2325)
  - Polish poster: announcement of military purchase of horses in market square, 1936, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2326)
  - Polish poster: announcement of military purchase of horses in market square, 1936, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2327)
  - Group of Luboml artifacts, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2328)
  - Hand painted New Year's card, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2329)
    Donated by Nechama (Weiner) Blau
  - Hand painted New Year's card, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2330)
  - Hand painted New Year's card, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2331)
  - Hand painted New Year's card, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2332)
    Donated by Nechama (Weiner) Blau. See P.7.7 for front of card and translation.
  - Postcard, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2333)
  - Postcard, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2334)
  - Postcard, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2335)
  - Postcard, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2336)
  - Postcard, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2337)
  - Savings book, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2338)
  - Savings book, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2339)
  - Savings book, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2340)
  - Savings book, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2341)
  - Savings book, 1 color transparency (Box-folder 71/2342)
  - Pharmacy banner, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2343)
  - Admission card, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2344)
  - Ticket to an evening dance, May 2, 1939, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2345)
  - Map, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2346)
  - Map, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2347)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2348)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2349)
  - A Village in Wolhynien, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2350)
  - A Village, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2351)
  - Windmill in Wolhynien, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2352)
  - Doctor's station, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2353)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2354)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2355)
  - Trees, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2356)
  - Building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2357)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2358)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2359)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2360)
  - Sports team, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2361)
  - Sports team, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2362)
  - Church, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2363)
  - Church, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2364)
  - Building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2365)
  - A portrait of a soldier, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2366)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2367)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2368)
  - Laboratory, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2369)
  - School building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2370)
  - Group inside Church building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2371)
  - Group inside Church building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2372)
  - Building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2372)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2373)
  - Village scene, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2374)
  - Men working on house, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2375)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2376)
  - Portrait of a woman, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2377)
  - Portrait of a man, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2378)
  - Married couple, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2379)
  - Soldiers, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2380)
  - Portrait of women, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2381)
  - Group picture, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2382)
  - Portrait of woman, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2383)
  - Portrait, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2384)
  - Portrait of man holding instrument, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2385)
  - Group playing instruments, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2386)
  - Building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2387)
  - Building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2388)
  - Religious ceremony, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2389)
  - Village scene, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2390)
  - Man in the woods, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2391)
  - Group of soldiers, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2392)
  - School building, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2393)
  - Group of soldiers, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2394)
  - Group of soldiers, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2395)
  - Religious parade, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2396)
  - Department of Film and Photography, Krejn, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2397)
  - Department of Film and Photography, Krejn, 1 black and white transparency (Box-folder 71/2398)
  - missing negatives (Box-folder 71/2399)
  - Picture of house (Box-folder 71/2400)
  - Picture of house (Box-folder 71/2401)
  - Map of Poland (Box-folder 71/2402)
  - Map of Poland (Box-folder 71/2403)
  - Catholic Church (Box-folder 71/2404)
  - Catholic Church (Box-folder 71/2405)
  - Catholic Church (Box-folder 71/2406)
  - Color postcard, hay sticks (Box-folder 71/2407)
  - Color postcard, hay sticks (Box-folder 71/2408)
  - Color postcard, hay sticks (Box-folder 71/2409)
- Series 4: Moving images